♪Every breath is my♪
♪كل نفس لي♪
♪Honest narration♪
♪رواية صادقة♪
♪Love doesn't have to be spoken out loud♪
♪الحب لا يجب أن يُقال بصوت عالٍ♪
=See Your Love=
=انظر حبك=
=Episode 3=
=الحلقة 3=
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Did he just slam the door close in front of me?
هل أغلق الباب أمامي للتو؟
(I don't want to be your care worker.)
(لا أريد أن أكون عامل الرعاية الخاص بك.)
Have I been rejected?
هل تم رفضي؟
You have been rejected.
لقد تم رفضك.
- Forget it if he doesn't want to do it. - No. I need a care worker.
- انسي الأمر إذا كان لا يريد القيام بذلك. - لا. أنا بحاجة إلى عامل رعاية.
You are afraid that our secrets will get exposed if we hire someone.
أنت خائف من أن أسرارنا سوف تنكشف إذا قمنا بتعيين شخص ما.
He's deaf.
إنه أصم.
Perfect for the job.
مثالية لهذه الوظيفة.
No one will ask a deaf person to be a corporate espionage.
لن يطلب أحد من شخص أصم أن يكون جاسوسًا للشركات.
I want him.
انا أريده.
I don't have anything much but money.
ليس لدي أي شيء سوى المال.
I can give you a high salary, food and accommodation provided.
أستطيع أن أعطيك راتبًا مرتفعًا، وتوفير الطعام والسكن.
You just have to be my care worker.
كل ما عليك فعله هو أن تكون عامل الرعاية الخاص بي.
Are you unsatisfied with the job or me?
هل أنت غير راضٍ عن الوظيفة أو عني؟
You are quite heartless.
أنت بلا قلب تماما.
How about this?
ماذا عن هذا؟
If you become my care worker,
إذا أصبحت عامل الرعاية الخاص بي،
I'll recommend you to the Xin'an Long-Term Care Center.
سأوصيك بمركز Xin'an للرعاية طويلة الأمد.
You marked it with five stars on your memo.
لقد قمت بوضع علامة خمس نجوم على مذكرتك.
It's the place where you want to work at the most.
إنه المكان الذي تريد العمل فيه أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
I can do that for you.
أستطيع أن أفعل ذلك من أجلك.
Other than money, I have a lot of friends too.
إلى جانب المال، لدي الكثير من الأصدقاء أيضًا.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
He's not so easy to convince.
ليس من السهل إقناعه.
Is everything okay there?
هل كل شيء على ما يرام هناك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
You are right.
أنت محق.
Yes. I've heard from Shuhe.
نعم لقد سمعت من شوهي.
He hasn't had any luck in finding a job yet.
ولم يحالفه الحظ في العثور على عمل حتى الآن.
Of course I still worry.
بالطبع لا أزال أشعر بالقلق.
Your son is back.
لقد عاد ابنك.
You are back.
لقد عدت.
You could've talked at home.
كان بإمكانك التحدث في المنزل.
Why did you have to go out?
لماذا كان عليك الخروج؟
(I don't know him well.)
(لا أعرفه جيدا.)
Your dad.
والدك.
(Ask him to do his best in the competition.)
(اطلب منه أن يبذل قصارى جهده في المنافسة.)
Your son asked you to do your best in the competition.
لقد طلب منك ابنك أن تبذل قصارى جهدك في المسابقة.
He said, "I got it. Thank you.".
قال "لقد حصلت عليه. شكرا لك".
(I'll go back to my room first.)
(سأعود إلى غرفتي أولاً.)
Of course I still worry about him.
بالطبع لا أزال أشعر بالقلق عليه.
It wasn't easy for him to go through his university studies. He put in so much effort.
لم يكن من السهل عليه إكمال دراسته الجامعية، فقد بذل الكثير من الجهد.
The lecturers said that he did very well too.
وقال المحاضرون أنه نجح بشكل جيد للغاية أيضًا.
He even got a professional certification.
حتى أنه حصل على شهادة مهنية.
But what happened in the end?
ولكن ماذا حدث في النهاية؟
After he graduated,
بعد تخرجه،
who would've expected that he couldn't find a job because he was deaf?
من كان يتوقع أنه لن يتمكن من العثور على عمل لأنه أصم؟
Okay now. I can't talk anymore.
حسنًا الآن، لا أستطيع التحدث بعد الآن.
I need to make dinner first.
أحتاج إلى تحضير العشاء أولاً.
Talk to you later. Bye.
سأتحدث معك لاحقًا. مع السلامة.
(Recruitment)
(توظيف)
But first, let me eat.
ولكن أولا، دعني آكل.
Did you have to make it sound so obscene?
هل كان عليك أن تجعل الأمر يبدو فاحشًا إلى هذا الحد؟
I didn't.
لم أكن.
I just woke up.
استيقظت للتو.
If you can't satisfy my appetite,
إذا لم تتمكن من إشباع شهيتي،
how can I satisfy your inhumane workaholic tendency?
كيف يمكنني إشباع ميلك اللاإنساني إلى العمل؟
Someone who works diligently won't die of hunger.
من يعمل بجد لن يموت من الجوع.
But most of them will die from illnesses.
لكن معظمهم سيموتون بسبب الأمراض.
Jonathan.
جوناثان.
I won't look handsome if I get any thinner.
لن أبدو وسيما إذا أصبحت أنحف.
(Are you gangsters?)
(هل أنتم رجال عصابات؟)
As long as I can achieve my goal, does it matter?
ما دام بإمكاني تحقيق هدفي، فهل يهم؟
Young Boss.
رئيس شاب.
We are not gangsters.
نحن لسنا رجال عصابات.
We are businessmen.
نحن رجال أعمال.
(Are you sure you can get me a job at Xin'an Long-Term Care Center?)
(هل أنت متأكد من أنك تستطيع أن تحصل لي على وظيفة في مركز شينآن للرعاية طويلة الأمد؟)
I promise.
أعدك.
So, I have only one question for you.
إذن، لدي سؤال واحد فقط لك.
Yes or no?
نعم أو لا؟
Then feed me first.
ثم أطعمني أولا.
Let me show you around first.
دعني أريك المكان أولاً.
This is the living room.
هذه غرفة المعيشة.
There's a public bathroom on the right side.
هناك حمام عام على الجانب الأيمن.
The laundry room is just beside the kitchen.
غرفة الغسيل تقع بجوار المطبخ مباشرة.
The second floor is like what I showed you just now.
الطابق الثاني هو مثل ما أريتكم للتو.
This is Young Boss's room.
هذه غرفة الرئيس الشاب.
Your room is on the second floor.
غرفتك في الطابق الثاني.
When I go out for work, keep a close eye on him.
عندما أخرج للعمل، أراقبه عن كثب.
If he does anything fishy,
إذا فعل أي شيء مريب،
inform me at once.
أخبرني على الفور.
(He is my boss.)
(هو مديري.)
I'm the one who will be paying you.
أنا من سيدفع لك .
I'm very easy to get along with.
من السهل جدًا التعامل معي.
You just have to remember one thing.
كل ما عليك فعله هو أن تتذكر شيئًا واحدًا.
Do not enter my room
لا تدخل غرفتي
without my permission.
بدون إذني.
Even if you want to wake me up.
حتى لو كنت تريد أن توقظني.
You can call me or knock on the door.
يمكنك الاتصال بي أو طرق الباب.
But you can't enter my room without my permission.
ولكن لا يمكنك الدخول إلى غرفتي دون إذني.
(I need your health report and food preferences.)
(أحتاج إلى تقريرك الصحي وتفضيلاتك الغذائية.)
No problem. I'll leave everything in your care.
لا مشكلة سأترك كل شيء تحت رعايتك.
You suddenly found a job where you had to move in with your boss.
لقد وجدت فجأة وظيفة تتطلب منك الانتقال للعيش مع رئيسك في العمل.
And you have to keep the location a secret.
ويجب عليك إبقاء الموقع سرا.
How can your dad not worry about you?
كيف يمكن لأبيك أن لا يقلق عليك؟
I'm not at home because I'm leading a team to compete outside.
أنا لست في المنزل لأنني أقود فريقًا للتنافس في الخارج.
Of course I'm worried about you.
بالطبع أنا قلق عليك.
How's the person you are caring for?
كيف حال الشخص الذي تهتم به؟
(He gets hungry very easily.)
(إنه يشعر بالجوع بسهولة.)
(His personality is a little bit strange.)
(شخصيته غريبة بعض الشيء.)
(But he is paying me well.)
(لكنه يدفع لي جيدا.)
(And the articles in the contract are reasonable too.)
(والمواد في العقد معقولة أيضًا.)
(Don't worry.)
(لا تقلق.)
That's good. You can come home if you can't get used to it.
هذا جيد، يمكنك العودة إلى المنزل إذا لم تتمكن من التعود على ذلك.
Come home.
تعال إلى المنزل.
You can always look for another job.
يمكنك دائمًا البحث عن وظيفة أخرى.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
لا تكن قاسياً على نفسك.
The whole family pays a lot of attention
العائلة كلها تولي اهتماما كبيرا
to your performance in Taiwan, China.
إلى أدائك في تايوان، الصين.
Dad, I don't want to...
أبي لا أريد...
You are not allowed to fail!
لا يجوز لك الفشل!
If you fail, don't bother coming back.
إذا فشلت فلا تفكر في العودة.
But won't he seem
ولكن ألن يبدو؟
too fragile if he comes home because he faces some hardships?
هل يكون هشًا جدًا إذا عاد إلى المنزل لأنه يواجه بعض الصعوبات؟
You are right.
أنت محق.
Then you should bully them back
ثم يجب عليك أن تتنمر عليهم مرة أخرى
before you come back.
قبل أن تعود.
Do as your dad says.
افعل كما يقول والدك.
It's rare to see him being such a baddie.
من النادر أن نراه بهذا الشكل الشرير.
(I know.)
(أنا أعرف.)
(You taught me before.)
(لقد علمتني من قبل.)
(If someone upsets me, I'll make their lives miserable too.)
(إذا أزعجني شخص ما، فسوف أجعل حياته بائسة أيضًا.)
But you have to take care of his three meals.
ولكن عليك الاهتمام بوجباته الثلاث.
How about I make the meals
ماذا عن أن أقوم بإعداد الوجبات؟
and get them delivered to you?
وتوصيلها إليك؟
(I have to keep the address a secret.)
(يجب أن أبقي العنوان سرا.)
(You taught me how to cook.)
(لقد علمتني كيف أطبخ.)
(You need to have confidence in me.)
(يجب أن تكون لديك الثقة بي.)
Look at your son.
أنظر إلى ابنك.
He has surpassed you.
لقد تفوق عليك.
Watch your words.
انتبه لكلماتك
Are you saying that my son can cook better than me?
هل تقول أن ابني يستطيع الطبخ أفضل مني؟
That's not what I meant.
هذا ليس ما قصدته.
Honey, I...
عزيزتي، أنا...
Suddenly, I want to drink a glass of juice.
فجأة، أريد أن أشرب كوبًا من العصير.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
The person I chose is not bad, right?
الشخص الذي اخترته ليس سيئا، أليس كذلك؟
The standard of our three meals has improved so much.
لقد تحسن مستوى وجباتنا الثلاث كثيرًا.
Our food is cooked to order.
يتم طهي طعامنا حسب الطلب.
We can ask for both hot drinks and cold drinks.
يمكننا طلب المشروبات الساخنة والمشروبات الباردة.
He's not bad.
إنه ليس سيئا.
It's one of the rare times when you make the right decision.
إنها واحدة من الأوقات النادرة التي تتخذ فيها القرار الصحيح.
Young Boss.
رئيس شاب.
Young Boss!
رئيس شاب!
Jiang Shaopeng, what did you do?
جيانغ شاوبنغ، ماذا فعلت؟
Yang Zixiang.
يانغ زيشيانغ.
How is he?
كيف حاله؟
Yang Zixiang!
يانغ زيشيانغ!
The doctor said you did very well.
قال الطبيب أنك قمت بعمل جيد جدًا.
(It was my duty. What happened?)
(لقد كان واجبي. ماذا حدث؟)
He's allergic to kiwis.
إنه يعاني من حساسية تجاه الكيوي.
How useless is he
كم هو عديم الفائدة
to not know what he's allergic to?
لا أعرف ما هو الشيء الذي يسبب له الحساسية؟
(Is he going to expose me?)
(هل سوف يفضحني؟)
I'll confirm it with the doctor
سأؤكد ذلك مع الطبيب
to see if he's allergic to anything else.
لنرى ما إذا كان يعاني من حساسية تجاه أي شيء آخر.
I'm not that impressed with this young boss.
أنا لست معجبًا بهذا الرئيس الشاب.
thank you for saving him in time.
شكرا لك على انقاذه في الوقت المناسب.
You are not bad.
أنت لست سيئا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
(Pretending to sleep is not a long-term solution.)
(التظاهر بالنوم ليس حلاً على المدى الطويل.)
I need to live in the now.
أحتاج أن أعيش في الوقت الحاضر.
One moment can become forever.
لحظة واحدة يمكن أن تصبح إلى الأبد.
I will go to Kaohsiung with Song Shuhe tomorrow
سأذهب إلى كاوهسيونج مع سونغ شو هي غدًا
to scout at the site.
لاستكشاف الموقع.
You can rest at home.
يمكنك الراحة في المنزل.
Yang Zixiang?
يانغ زيشيانغ؟
Not many people know me in Taiwan, China.
لا يعرفني الكثير من الناس في تايوان، الصين.
You can become Yang Zixiang.
يمكنك أن تصبح يانغ Zixiang.
don't tell anyone about it
لا تخبر أحدا بذلك
and ask Shuhe to keep it a secret,
وأطلب من شوهي أن يبقي الأمر سراً،
everyone will be happy.
الجميع سيكونون سعداء.
What else can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل أيضًا؟
I have a business trip tomorrow. I'll be back at night.
لدي رحلة عمل غدًا، وسأعود في الليل.
I'll leave everything to you.
سأترك لك كل شيء.
(You deliberately drank Fengjie's juice.)
(لقد شربت عصير فينجي عمداً.)
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
A serious allergic reaction can kill someone.
يمكن أن تؤدي ردود الفعل التحسسية الخطيرة إلى وفاة شخص ما.
Even if I wanted to fake an illness to take a sick leave,
حتى لو أردت أن أتظاهر بالمرض لأخذ إجازة مرضية،
I wouldn't risk my own life to do that.
لن أخاطر بحياتي من أجل القيام بذلك.
I'm not that brave.
أنا لست شجاعا إلى هذه الدرجة.
(Really?)
(حقًا؟)
Of course.
بالطبع.
Just do your job,
فقط قم بعملك
earn your money,
اكسب أموالك
and take what you deserve.
وخذ ما تستحقه
Don't care about anything else.
لا أهتم بأي شيء آخر.
After we failed last time, Yang Zixiang went into hiding.
بعد أن فشلنا في المرة الأخيرة، ذهب يانغ زيكسيانج للاختباء.
Hongcheng has been very secretive about it too.
وكانت هونغتشنغ سرية للغاية بشأن هذا الأمر أيضًا.
I'll send someone to investigate.
سأرسل شخصًا للتحقيق.
I'll get it done.
سأقوم بإنجازه.
I wouldn't have agreed if I knew this would be so troublesome.
لم أكن لأوافق لو كنت أعلم أن هذا سيكون مزعجًا للغاية.
Find Yang Zixiang and take care of him.
ابحث عن يانغ زيكسيانج واعتني به.
Destroy the collaboration between those two companies.
تدمير التعاون بين الشركتين.
If you can do that,
إذا كان بإمكانك فعل ذلك،
I'll consider your debt paid off.
سأعتبر دينك مسددًا.
Then I'll give you a gang to lead.
ثم سأعطيك عصابة لقيادتها.
He can lead a gang if he gets rid of Yang Zixiang?
هل يستطيع قيادة العصابة إذا تخلص من يانغ زيكسيانج؟
Who is Yang Zixiang?
من هو يانغ زيشيانغ؟
Why is Dong offering so much to take him down?
لماذا يقدم دونغ الكثير لإسقاطه؟
Shut up.
اسكت.
Dong would kill me if he found out that I eavesdropped on them.
سيقتلني دونغ إذا اكتشف أنني أتنصت عليهم.
Did you...
هل فعلت...؟
What did you hear this time?
ماذا سمعت هذه المرة؟
I've found a chance to prove myself.
لقد وجدت فرصة لإثبات نفسي.
If I succeed, I can be a gang leader.
إذا نجحت، أستطيع أن أكون زعيم العصابة.
I'll leave it to you to take care of the house.
سأترك لك مهمة العناية بالمنزل.
Be good.
كن جيدا.
What can I do when I can't even walk?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل عندما لا أستطيع حتى المشي؟
Have a safe journey.
أتمنى لك رحلة آمنة.
Give me a glass of water.
أعطني كوبًا من الماء.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I didn't do it on purpose.
لم أفعل ذلك عمدا.
Take your time.
خذ وقتك.
You can take a shower.
يمكنك الاستحمام.
I can eat by myself.
أستطيع أن أتناول الطعام بنفسي.
You are so fast.
أنت سريع جدًا.
(I just changed my pants.)
(لقد غيرت سروالي للتو.)
You are right.
أنت محق.
(I should've asked for juice just now.)
(كان ينبغي لي أن أطلب العصير الآن.)
(My distance from the door.)
(مسافاتي من الباب.)
It's just seven. And you are drinking so much already.
إنها السابعة فقط، وأنت تشرب الكثير بالفعل.
It's too early.
إنه مبكر جداً.
The early bird catches the worm.
الطائر المبكر يلتقط الدودة.
But there aren't many worms here.
ولكن لا يوجد الكثير من الديدان هنا.
There will be more worms after 10.
سيكون هناك المزيد من الديدان بعد 10.
The important thing is not the quantity.
المهم ليس الكمية .
The important thing is, will they catch my fancy?
الأمر المهم هو، هل سوف يجذبون انتباهي؟
This one is my treat.
هذا هو علاجي.
Finally, I managed to leave.
وأخيرا تمكنت من المغادرة.
Now, even if the project is a success,
الآن، حتى لو كان المشروع ناجحًا،
it has nothing to do with me.
لا علاقة لي بهذا الأمر.
♪The city grooms the shadows of the two people♪
♪المدينة تعتني بظلال الشخصين♪
♪The sunset will awaken the memories♪
♪غروب الشمس سوف يوقظ الذكريات♪
♪At that moment, no names are needed♪
♪في تلك اللحظة، ليست هناك حاجة إلى أسماء♪
♪Let the world burn to dust♪
♪دع العالم يحترق إلى غبار♪
♪You are the only one who can protect me♪
♪أنت الوحيد الذي يستطيع حمايتي♪
♪We can decide on our own touching story♪
♪يمكننا أن نقرر قصتنا المؤثرة بأنفسنا♪
♪Nothing can replace this soundless love♪
لا شيء يمكن أن يحل محل هذا الحب الصامت
♪I stop talking when I see you running away from me every day♪
♪أتوقف عن الحديث عندما أراك تهرب مني كل يوم♪
♪I'm afraid to think about you, I'm losing you♪
♪أخاف أن أفكر فيك، فأنا أفقدك♪
♪I look for you from the sea of people♪
♪أبحث عنك من بين بحر الناس♪
♪I want to say I love you♪
♪أريد أن أقول أنني أحبك♪
♪I convey my love for you through the tips of our fingers♪
♪أعبر لك عن حبي من خلال أطراف أصابعنا♪
♪I can only wait like a fool because I can't hear anything♪
♪لا أستطيع إلا الانتظار مثل الأحمق لأنني لا أستطيع سماع أي شيء♪
♪I long to live in your heart♪
♪أتمنى أن أعيش في قلبك♪
♪I want to stop, I want to give up♪
♪أريد أن أتوقف، أريد أن أستسلم♪
♪I want to forget how much effort we've put into this♪
♪أريد أن أنسى مقدار الجهد الذي بذلناه في هذا الأمر♪
♪I can't forget about our promise on that day♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أنسى وعدنا في ذلك اليوم♪
I found you.
لقد وجدت لك.
Yang Zixiang.
يانغ زيشيانغ.
You didn't take good care of him.
لم تعتني به جيدا.